welcome to the manulife group benefits
site
today i'm going to show you how easy it
is to submit claims
update your personal information
learn about your benefits
and more
once you're signed in your homepage will
come up
from here you can do just about
everything you'll need to do
you can submit a claim
get a digital copy of your benefits card
or send us a change of beneficiary form
you'll also find details of your most
recent health and dental claims
for each entry you'll see the type of
service provided who it was for and the
status of the claim here you'll see how
much the claim was for and how much was
covered
if you have a question about a claim you
can send us a secure email here
if you see an exclamation mark beside a
claim it means that we need more
information before we can process it
click on the exclamation mark to find
out what's missing
you can send us the information from
here and we'll take another look at your
claim
in this section you can also check your
available balances next to the your
claims tab
if you want to know about your coverage
go to the my benefits section
switch between the tabs to see the
different kinds of coverage you have and
how much
go to my profile to update your personal
information banking information or to
change your password
in the top menu you'll find many of the
same functions we just covered but take
a closer look at the forms tab
this is where you'll find digital
beneficiary forms or optional life
insurance application forms
fill out the form and send it to us here
and finally if your company has a
retirement program with manulife you'll
find a link to your retirement savings
account here
[Music]
these are just some of the ways manulite
makes managing your benefits easy and
secure
[Music]